



Website LinkedIn ugurcengiz.com in/ugurcengiz

I'm Fullstack Developer with 5 years experience. I develop web applications, micro services, mobile applications and mobile games. Technologies i use frequently are Laravel, React.js, Vue, Node.js, SQL, Postman, Linux, Docker. I consider following coming updates and innovations in the software field. I can manage development process of projects using tools like Git, Tests, Docker, CI/CD deployment automations.

Work experience

Fullstack Developer 2020 - 2023

Tagum, İzmir

I developed e-Invoice automation system that works with extremely large JSON files and it converts, parses data to UBL standarted e-invoice objects and saves to database.

I developed ERP application and wrote additional modules to integrate with another external web API services like Trendyol API, Hepsiburada API and a couple more to handle accounting processes and send them to automations.

I developed micro apps to handle checking web applications, api services's health and trigger related automations in case of unexptected in-app crashes.

Backend Developer 2017 - 2018

Bulrog, İzmir

I build corporate and commercial websites, wrote wordpress plugins and custom email design templates

Backend Developer 2016 - 2017

Calisto, İzmir

I developed CRM application for company and wrote needed features.

Education and Qualifications

Associate Degree 2022 - Present

Bandırma Üniversitesi, Balıkesir/Gönen

Computer Programming / Distance Learning

Languages

English

Skills

Laravel

Node.js

Javascript

React.js

C#

Linux

Docker